

Mario Elisei Neto
Born in Sao Paulo,

Graphic / Web Designer

Graphic Design:

Create branding, magazine, printed catalogs, brochures, promotional items, posters, packing, CD covers, newsletters, banners, video editing and motion, business card, folder, books, flyer.

Web Developer:

Wordpress, LAMP (Linux, Apache, MySQL, PHP), JSON, HTML4/5, HTTP/S, XML, CSS, APIs, REST, advanced knowledge in web designing tools - SEO, Google Analytics / Ads, animated GIFs (banners) from web.

Tools:

Expert in Adobe Creative Cloud Illustrator, Photoshop, After Effects, InDesign, and Final Cut, very ease of learning new tools.

Platform:

Advanced Mac OS (Macintosh).

Follow me

- (in) linkedin.com/in/marioelisei
- Bē be.net/marioelisei
- (a) instagram/marioelisei

Contact me

- (S) @m.elisei

+1 (267) 629-6920

Objective

Graphic / Web Design - Full Stack Designer

Personal Summary

Professional with over 19 years of experience with solid knowledge in technology and graphic design, web developer UI/UX. Working with large design companies, agencies, clients in Brazil and worldwide with: Graphic Design, WebDesign/Developer and Social Media Strategy.

I also work on the Lululemon Canada Team as a Graphic Designer freelancer.

Experience

Self-Employed

Graphic Designer / Web Developer UI UX 2015 - current

- Successfully managed graphic/web design projects from concept through to completion. This includes strategic planning, tests, and digital presentations, as well as briefings, creations, development, and printing.
- Administration of social media and websites.

IBM

IT Specialist | Design Solutions 2009 - 2015

- IT specialist pre-sales, architecture, and design solutions to large computers.
- Support graphic design to the marketing sales area.
- Training of clients and partners.

Self-Employed

Graphic and Web Designer 2004 - 2009

Successful projects for:

IBM, Coca Cola, Samsung, Epson, Master Card, Motorola, Bayer, Banco Santander, Banco Itaú and various other Brazilian companies.

Education

- Computer Engineer(bachelor degree)
- Automation Engineering (postgraduate)
- Packaging and Graphic Designer
- Art Director
- Design Thinking
- UI Design
- Golden Ratio on Design

Languages

English intermediatePortuguese FluentSpanish Basic